

STEFANO BRAMBILLA



I am a **Mathematical Engineer** with a solid background in conceiving and **developing AI solutions** to address complex business problems. My expertise includes creating **prediction and classification ML models** and managing **NLP models** such as LLM, and **deploying** them into production. I stand out for my ability to identify **business needs** and conceive appropriate **architectural solutions**.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PROPOSAL LEADER Moxoff 2023 - today

- Head of the technical management of the pre-sales phase for Al projects, I
 dealt with qualifying commercial opportunities, exploring customer data,
 making preliminary choices of solution models, designing the solution
 architecture, and drafting the technical specifications and project proposals.
- I led a team of two people, managing task assignments and establishing weekly priorities.
- I successfully contributed to the sale of over 20 projects in one year, out of over 100 project proposals developed, covering various solutions, including the prediction of production quality from machine sensors, a chatbot for automate the help desk and a chatbot for drive-thru at a fastfood restaurant.

MATH MODELS DEVELOPER Moxoff 2019-2022

- Developer in over 15 Data Science projects with a focus on defining models, implementing backend code, and automation using Docker and CI/CD pipelines.
- Development of a Python solution for time series forecasting applied to HV
 energy flow in northern Italy, through the ensemble of models developed
 with Tensorflow and XGBoost and deployed with Sagemaker.
- Creation of a solution for Big Data processing in the advertising sector using Apache Spark, with related infrastructure on AWS, and subsequent maintenance with technical leadership.
- Maintenance of production code for a recommendation system and development of new features in Agile mode.
- Active member of the Competence Center for Distributed Computing, introducing the use of Terraform as a company practice

EDUCATION

Mathematical Engineering MSc, Politecnico di Milano

Mathematical and physical modelling for biomedicine 2015-2018 104/110

Mathematical Engineering BSc, Politecnico di Milano 2012-2015 105/110





CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Certified Solutions
 Architect – Associate (2022)



 Machine Learning with Python - MITx (2023)



COMPETENCES

- Python, C++, Scala, Node.is,
- Tensorflow, Scikit-Learn, LangChain, XGBoost
- Terraform, AWS, GCP, Azure, SageMaker
- Docker, Kubernetes, Git, Bash
- Apache Spark, React, Streamlit
- Apache Spark, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch
- NGINX, Keycloack, Letsencrypt
- Classification and Prediction ML Models
- NLP and GenAl Models
- Data Manipulation and ETL Pipelines
- Optimization Problems
- Development and use of RESTful APIs
- Implementation of CI/CD Pipeline
- Development of simple User Interfaces
- English Proficiency Level C1 (IELTS 2014)
- Distinctive ability to identify business needs and formulate effective strategies for solving complex problems
- Multitasking skills demonstrated in dynamic and challenging environments
- Experience in Agile methodology, with the ability to adapt to flexible and collaborative development processes
- Passionate about 3D printing, comics basketball, and board games
- Active blood donor for AVIS

CONTACT



<u>392 381 5974</u>



s.brambilla93@gmail.com



stefano-brambilla-82811135



Milano